<speak>
    <!-- slide 1 -->
    <p>
        Introducing Pistol DDS.  Pistol DDS makes creating peer to peer as well as traditional REST or RPC applications simple
    </p>
    <p>
        This is because all application code is client side.  No longer will you need to write code for the client side
        <break/>and<break/>  duplicate effort writing code for the server <break/>allowing for faster updates which is
        perfect for agile development.
    </p>

    <!-- slide 2-->

        <p>
            In this short video, we will demonstrate some of the additional benefits of <break time="70ms"/> Pistol DDS <break time="70ms"/>including:
            <break/>
            The pistol security layer,
            <break/>
            How pistol provides built in data redundancy,
            <break/>
            How to setup pistol DDS for the level of control, security, and privacy  you want.
            And.
            How pistol DDS provides sensorship resistance for your social app.
        </p>

    <!-- slide 3 -->
    <p>
        Pistol DDS allows you to write peer-to-peer apps without worrying about servers or databases.
        You can write mobile, web or desktop applications as well as services using Javascript or Typescript with your
        favorite frameworks.
        Currently, Pistol comes with a library for React.
    </p>

    <!-- slide 4 -->

    All of this means that you can write your applications, faster and easier,
    with less time troubleshooting, or worrying about deploying your application, which, reduces the overall cost.

    Also, end-to-end testing becomes easier since there is no server or database to worry about.

    <!-- slide 5 -->
    To accomplish this, Pistol treats everything as a peer on the network.  Mobile devices, computers and service nodes
    are all equal peers on the network.  Peers can pull data from other peers on the network.  After they do, they
    can share data on the network with other peers.  This provides data redundancy for data that people care about.


    <!-- slide 6 -->
    You might be asking at this point, if everything is a peer, how do we ensure data integrity and security?

    <!-- slide 7 -->
    <p>
        There are four security models for a piece of data.  Public<break time="250ms"/> write-only<break time="250ms"/> Owner writable while others can read<break time="250ms"/>,
        and, Data that is private to the owner.
    </p>
    <p>
        Each one of these models uses a single or a combination of encryption or verification methods that were borrowed
        from blockchain technology.
    </p>

    <!-- slide 8 -->
    With pistol, redundancy is automatic for the reasons stated before.

    <!-- slide 9 -->
    When an application requires a peace of data, it will ask the network for that data.  If someone else has that
    data, they can provide it on demand.

    <!-- slide 10 -->
    When another application asks for that same peace of data, multiple peers will be able to provide it.

    <!-- slide 11 -->
    A design consideration for Pistol was maximum flexibility for the users, and application developers.
    Pistol does not dictate which security model you use, or what services you can provide.  That is up to you.

    You can run anything from a fully moderated forum to a fully decentralized uncontrolled video site.  You are the boss.

    <!-- slide 12 -->
    Here are three examples of possible network configurations.  One with a service connected into the DDS network,
    one with a blockchain, and one where the end user applications are traditional REST or RPC endpoints.

    As you can see, DDS can provide redundancy for third party services for your end users as well.

    There are too many possible configurations to list here, but hopefully you get the idea.

    <!-- slide 13 -->
    Because Pistol is peer-to-peer first, censorship resistance becomes a side-effect.  As long as multiple other
    devices have the data that you want, you can always retrieve it.

    <!-- slide 14 -->
    To summarize, Pistol DDS makes development easy, provides redundancy and censorship resistance, all while giving you
    full control of your application and data.

    <!-- slide 15 -->
    Thank you for watching.  And, to get started, follow the instructions in the “Getting Started”
    menu to install the Pistol DDS starter kit.

</speak>